HAYDEN NEUMEYER

SUMMARY

Recent graduate proficient in Networking, Virtualization, and Microsoft Server Technologies pursuing a rewarding career in Information Technology utilizing my skills, talents, and experience to support the mission and professional effectiveness of any business or organization.

CONTACT

■ hadn.neumeyer@gmail.com

A hadn69.com

4 618 476 3306

in hadn69

nadn69

EDUCATION

Ranken Technical College

A.S. Computer Technology 2016

Southern Illinois University Edwardsville Computer Science

EXPERIENCE

r/AlienMC

Head Administrator

2012 to Current

Ensure smooth operation of all game servers, consistent communication with the community, and stability of all related services: website, Discord, IRC, and Mumble.

Recent achievements include:

Setting up automated backups

Deploying new server instances using docker

Deploying a new web control panel for all services

SIUE Solar Car Team

Edwardsville, IL 2014 to 2014

Assistant Project Director

Coordinate between all divisions of the team to insure compatible

designs, safety of designs, and implementation.

Achievements in this position include:

Designing, fabricating, and installing a new solar panel array

Coordinating work days

Coordination of the fabrication of new parts

SIUE Solar Car Team

Edwardsville, IL

Mechanical Director

2013 to 2014

In charge of all mechanical design, fabrication, and implementation,

including computer modeling and simulation.

Achievements in this position include:

Passing all safety checks during our first ever race

Performing finite element analysis to test the structure of the frame

design

Fabrication of structural reinforcement

CERTIFICATIONS

MCPS: Microsoft Certified Professional

MCTS: Windows 7, Configuration

CompTIA A+

SKILLS

Windows 7, Linux, Troubleshooting, Computer Hardware, Windows Server, Windows, Networking, Solar Energy, Matlab, Public Speaking, Programming, C++, PHP, Python